<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The LAS Manifesto</title>
    <link>https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The LAS Manifesto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 14:18:09 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Events</title>
      <link>https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/issues/2-decentralized-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 14:18:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/issues/2-decentralized-events/</guid>
      <description>A lot of us are busy at different times in the semester. I have observed that many of you are interested in essay-writing, debates, JAMs, and want to participate in events/competitions held in the institute, but your academic schedule doesn&amp;rsquo;t accommodate your interests. What if you can organize an event yourself, however and whenever you like?
With guidance from a literary affairs council member, any student in the institute will be able to organize an event with their own rules, with the date and topic/theme/language of their choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 16:29:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/about-me/</guid>
      <description>To me, writing isn&amp;rsquo;t just a means for communication. It&amp;rsquo;s a tool for retrospection, a mechanism for change. Words have the power to connect like minded people. And the best part is when the reader comes back and talks to you about what you wrote!
I wrote stories and articles but somehow ended up not sharing them publicly. That ended with Udaan (It&amp;rsquo;s an amazing newsletter and it&amp;rsquo;s growing, so please go read it if you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More than a Manifesto</title>
      <link>https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/issues/1-manifesto-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 16:29:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/issues/1-manifesto-website/</guid>
      <description>This is not just a manifesto but also an evolving list of ideas, which means that new ideas are added, outdated ideas are scrapped, and all progress about it&amp;rsquo;s implementation is continuously updated. I chose a website over other alternatives as there is high potential for customizability, and we have no shortage of techies in our institute! I encourage everyone who likes this idea to make use of it yourself, and improve on it if possible!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Manifesto</title>
      <link>https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 16:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pace577.github.io/literary-manifesto/manifesto/</guid>
      <description>I am Prabhat, a third year undergraduate student from the Electrical Engineering department (Batch of 2018). I am contesting for the post of Literary affairs secretary (LAS) in the Student Elections 2021-22 and this is my humble manifesto.
Intention The executive wing has done a very good job over the years in developing a literary environment in our college. We have a debating club, a quizzing club, a film club, a student newsletter, a good set of leisure reading books in the library, along with multiple literary events with prizes held around the year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
